You're awake.
How do you feel?
Do you have something to say to me?
I want to say I'm fine.
You don't need to worry.
When I recover,
can you tell me
the story of you and Miss Tang?
You killed her.
But I really didn't mean it.
Let me explain.
Give me a moment.
How dare you, Yuwen Jingxuan.
You really are cunning.
Please calm down, Your Highness.
Why not use our spies to poison them again, or...
Speak.
Dying at the hands of a lover,
or killing the one you love,
which is more painful?
If what Yuwen Jingxuan said is true...
She is me,
and I am her.
Then why was she killed
while I am still alive?
Can he foresee the future?
But,
I've definitely had this birthmark since I was born.
It can't be faked.
No.
I still need to go and ask him for clarification.
Guards!
Your Highness.
Make sure to hand this to Eldest Young Master Su personally.
Yes.
Are you alright, Miss Tang?
It was dangerous here just now.
I had no choice but to do this.
Dangerous?
At this point,
I can no longer keep it from you, Miss Tang.
Actually, you and the Miss Tang my sixth brother mentioned
are indeed the same person.
The reason why
I repeatedly asked you to leave
is because I fear history will repeat itself.
History
repeating itself?
You might have forgotten, Miss Tang.
My sixth brother has been lonely since childhood.
He is extreme and paranoid.
Last time, just because of a trivial matter,
he killed that girl.
Now, as for Prince Shuo's Mansion,
you can't go back.
Why don't I escort you out of the city, Miss Tang?
The world is vast,
and the martial world is wide.
There must be a way out for you.
But since I helped you fake your death last time,
I'm afraid once you disappear,
I'll be the first one they suspect.
Then what should we do?
Why don't we go all the way
and kill him?
Miss Tang.
Don't worry.
I will definitely help you clean up the mess.
No one will find out it was you.
Miss Tang,
you ended up like this today
all because of Yuwen Jingxuan.
If you don't kill him with your own hands,
are you going to wait
for him to kill you again?
Fine.
Since Miss Tang is so deeply in love,
I, as an outsider, will say no more.
Please leave, Miss.
Next year during the Qingming Festival,
I will burn a stick of incense for you.
Tang Zhiluo,
kill Yuwen Jingxuan.
Kill him.
Kill Yuwen Jingxuan.
Yuwen Jingxuan.
Miss Aduo,
we just met by chance.
Why do you keep following me?
It's been three days and three nights.
Aren't you tired?
Give me the jade thumb ring in your purse,
and I'll stop following you.
That won't do.
Why not?
That jade thumb ring is the token of the Su family's matriarch.
How can it be given to just anyone?
Isn't that perfect?
I'm going to marry you anyway.
It's all the same.
How can you say such things so casually?
Well, in the frontier...
This is not the frontier.
But I am from the frontier.
I don't care.
I am going to marry you.
Forget it.
It's getting late.
Let's find an inn for the night.
Walk slower.
Hey.
Too fast.
Mr. Su, this is a letter from the prince.
Keep an eye on the girl next door.
Don't let her find out I'm gone.
Jingxuan.
You must hold on until I get back.